You take out a mirror to be proof
You really kidnapped Sonoko.
Remained
Mirror wreckage
Such thing
Anyone other than me can do it
Besides
At the second kidnapping
I was outside the hotel
even
It was right next to Mr. Kogoro Mori.
At first glance
It seems impossible
for you to kidnap Ran.
But you can do it simply
by using some method
Very nasty way
Ran wasn't kidnapped.
Go out
myself
Maybe you
Ran secretly, threatening
- What?
-You probably have a spare key for the auditorium.
"Sonoko Suzuki was kidnapped
because he was mistaken for you"
'If you want to save your friend's life'
'Exit the main hall at noon'
'If I tell someone'
'There is no life for Sonoko'
After that
Disguise yourself as a hotel employee
Would have instructed you to come here
Ran with a strong sense of justice
Can't even talk to me
alone...
Using Ran's mind to
think about his friends
Committing a crime
Worst
It's really the worst
Mr. Azuma
Azuma, did you commit suicide?
It was on the news earlier
Suicide?
surely
Mr. Azuma was the culprit.
There must have been a will.
You lost
You now
You admitted to the crime.
How do you know?
That Mr. Azuma wrote a will.
-So in the news..
.-It can't be.
because
I brought it.
Before the police come.
I was just mistaken
On the news that
it seems suicidal
-Of course there must be a will..
.-You're really late to give up.
This will was threatened
by the real killer
It was written by Mr. Azuma.
As evidence
The real killer wrote
KIDNAPPER
nevertheless
Mr. Azuma wrote
KIDNAPER
One P is not enough
It’s not wrong to use anything
Usually one person
doesn't write in two letters
And
This will is conclusive
evidence that you are the culprit.
A message left by
Azuma with all his energy
So what about that?
'My kidnapper is my'
My kidnapper
It is you
You know you're here, right?
Why did I send you a challenge?
You used to
The man's ex-girlfriend I arrested
for working with the investigation
"Arrested warehouse company manager"
The man ran a warehouse rental company
Blinded by money because of
debt, he got his hands on crime.
And died in prison
No time now
Where are Ran and Sonoko?
Even if you do that,
you can’t run away.
I never thought of running
away from the beginning
Ran!
Ran, are you okay?
Shinichi
Stupid child
Behave whatever you want
sorry
Sorry for not noticing
this...
It was the best rescue
request you could ever make.
no
It was a sign that I believed
I thought you would come
Ran!
Now, let's all three die here
Are you inside!
Ran!
Damn it
Do it in moderation
To hate you hate your boyfriend
-Don't get us in
.-Right.
The person who committed the sin is bad
But i loved you
If you don't hate someone
Couldn't live
Life without him
Just save Ran
I am a precious person
More than my life
You seem to be
precious to that girl
so
It's pitiful if only you die
The girl left behind
Like me
I have to live the hellish days
-Ran isn't that weak
.-Is it really?
When you disappear
That girl must be...
You can't break up
No matter what
Shinichi!
Damn it
Go this time!
Thanks, uncle
It's really over now
Only white lines
What should I break?
No one
I made it so that I can never stop
So
I don't know
Shinichi?
It will be fine, Ran
So the case was resolved.
Come on
-Let's g
o-Yes
Dad
Sorry
Don't say anything
Thank you
For saving Ran
Thanks to your help
Rando
Sonoko found
nearby was also safe,
You!
What are you thinking about
taking evidence from the field!
Are you, a former detective?
Even without common sense, there is a degree!
But thanks to that will,
the case was solved.
This is another matter!
Me and the uncle were very scolded.
Entering that house
Ran participated in the karate
competition with the wound on his leg
Won a great job
I went to Tropical Land with
me to celebrate my victory.
That day
I didn't even know it would be the day of fate
An amusement park at this age
"Sherlock Holmes Case Collection"
"Conan Doyle"
Come on, let's go
quickly Mitsuhiko, Ayumi
Wait, Kenta
If you run like that, you fall
hurt
- OK?
- hurt
-What, there was
.-What, there was.
Go
Next, let's go ride the jet coaster
Isn't it the first time
since only those kids?
Coming to a place like this for two
is it?
Yes
I wasn't such a kid
Today goes back to that time
Let's have fun
Huh
Come to think of it
Actually, what were you trying to say?
then
If I run away from the confrontation
Maybe next time they
come in a more mean way
Besides...
I forgot
Let's go fast anyway
-Teach me
.-No
Besides
I didn't want to be nervous
Because it was the school
trip you expected so much
At Tropical Land, where I went with Ran
I witness suspicious
men in black clothes
-I followed them
.-I'll be there soon.
That was the last time I was
with Ran in the form of Shinichi.
After that I was
attacked by men in black
While I'm losing my mind
You will eat the mysterious poison.
And when I open my eyes
Body was shrinking
His name is God... not that
"Edogawa Ranpo, Conan Doyle"
Conan!
My name is Edogawa Conan!